[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 21, "question": "You had to say to yourself, this guy is one sick puppy, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 22, "answer": "Totally, especially after the first scandal had already happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "It's so bizarre, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "You know, he's one tick away from being just a complete perv to be honest with you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Isn't that the problem?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "It's a lack of core values.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"], "TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "And if Anthony Weiner cannot show the kind of judgment that is necessary, the loyalty to his family that is necessary, what makes you think that he would be the right person to lead the city on New York?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "I had an interview last night, I just wanted to talk to you about actually because it was about George Zimmerman, about guns.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anthony Weiner"], "LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "Where does that leave you if you're the one that supplied the gun?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "Well, if we're the ones that supplied the gun and remember, we provided money, not a gun, but if someone is on top of Mr. Zimmerman again repeatedly bashing his head into the concrete, and he acts in self-defense, that's incredible bad luck that he found himself in that situation twice, but we'll sleep soundly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Every time you point a gun at somebody and you're going to pull the trigger, think, is that life worth $5,000 for a bullet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NN", "$", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$5,000"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "NN", "VBZ", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VB", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "But actually, he's a very dangerous man, and the obvious question is how could he be in a position to even do this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "I think it's very important that when somebody is take into custody, that there is some assessment of dangerousness, risk level, because you want more security on a person that poses a risk.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "What do you do about this kind of thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "Well, as I said, you need to put people like this in the right facility.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ":", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "What is this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Well, my view on this Piers -- and thank you for inviting me on the show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "To Ben Ferguson, give me one good reason why arming 20 teachers and administrators is a sensible way to reduce gun violence in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "PRP", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "VBG", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "I've give you three.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben Ferguson"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "And before I go to Mary Cathryn Ricker, you would presumably by extension of your argument, Ben, you would arm every single teacher in America if you could in every school?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "No, absolutely not.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mary Cathryn Ricker", "Ben"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", ",", "EX", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "My huge concern is this idea that for every problem you think you may be solving, there are going to be far more pervasive problems that you're actually creating.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mary"]}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Are they keeping it locked and loaded?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "Mary, Mary --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Will they have time to go and unlock it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "You're -- this is where the fear-mongering is exhausting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "Explain to me how you'll do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "Well, you actually take the gun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "Where do the teachers put their guns physically?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "They wear it on their waist.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Mary?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Yes, so we're starting in the wrong place.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben"]}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "RB", ":", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 341, "question": "So what do you want to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "...of the school district actually said that so -- so first of all, Ben, I actually don't appreciate being accused of not doing my research because I've spent quite a bit of time talking to the...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "DT", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "So what do you want to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "...that these just are going to happen (ph).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1999"], "PERSON": ["Ben", "Mary", "Wayne Lapierre"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "CC", "NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "CD", ":", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "MD", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", "MD", "VB", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "...and we trust them with our kids, why would we not trust them with this?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "OK, but Ben, very quickly, last point to you and then a final point to Mary, why did Wayne Lapierre as early as 1999 -- why was he so adamant that shouldn't, by his words, that we saw at the top of the segment, there should be no guns at any school in America.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBD", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "Alan Dershowitz, are you surprised that Bradley Manning evaded a conviction for aiding the enemy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Well, evaded is not the word I would use.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alan Dershowitz", "Bradley Manning"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Daniel Ellsberg"]}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "Where is the line between whistle-blowing and becoming a traitor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "Well, in -- in our lifetime, Daniel Ellsberg, in my opinion, was a whistle-blower.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "So how do you regulate it going forward?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Well, the best way to keep a secret is not to know it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Middle East"]}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "VBP", ":", "IN", "RB", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "P.J. Crowley, just finally, instead of just saying (ph) John Kerry through the nine-month goal for Middle East peace talks today, is he being too optimistic do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "RB", "VBG", ":", "NN", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "Well, I think it's very important to have a Middle East peace process and having the parties talk even if the prospects of success are -- are not promising, I think is vitally important.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["P.J. Crowley", "John Kerry"], "LOCATION": ["Middle East"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "What is your reaction to that reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "It's interesting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "What is your wheel house, Brad paisley?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "I don't know anymore.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brad"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130730pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "Was she unfairly vilified, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "Oh, I don't know, I mean, I don't enough about what she really did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]